Lucas Bramas

Service & ux designer

Bordeaux, France French nationality - 26 years old +33 7 85 92 78 55 lucasbramas@protonmail.com linkedin.com/in/lucas-bramas lucasbramas.com My approach enables me to understand the experience of your project, its ecosystem and its actors in order to imagine and prototype the succession of interactions to be set up between your service and your users.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Service & ux designer Grand Lyon Métropole

September 2018 - October 2019 Lyon Project monitoring and multidisciplinary teamwork for the conceptualisation of digital public services for users. Redesigning services and ensuring product consistency.

Graphic designer Petit Shirt

January 2017 — February 2017 Grenoble

Creation of motifs and illustrations for a t-shirt and textile personalisation catalogue. Creation of web communication supports around BtoB offers.

Vice President

Association Design Camp

October 2017 — February 2019 Bordeaux Association promoting design projects in Bordeaux. Organisation of events presenting the work of student designers and meetings with professionals.

EDUCATION

University of Bordeaux III

2017 — 2019 Bordeaux Master's degree of design: interaction, innovation, service. Research thesis on citizen participation in public policies.

University of Nîmes

2014 — 2017 Nîmes Bachelor's degree of Applied Arts with a specialisation in design, option design and digital cultures. Diploma project on digital participatory democracy.

High School of Dauphiné

2012 — 2013 Romans-sur-Isère

Hard skills

Bachelor's degree in management science and technology with a marketing option.



ux / ui systemic vision business model user research ethnography facilitation user journey usage scenario prototyping

user testing

design fiction

Soft skills
figma
illustrator
xd
indesign
photoshop
premiere pro
lightroom
sketchup
rhino 3d
keyshot
html

CSS

p5.js

arduino





english

intermediate speaker

spanish
beginner speaker